<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KNIT</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="navigation_open">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_close">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="html"><![CDATA[<p>The general welfare of the students is looked after by the Dean of Students Welfare.<br/><br/>
<h3><font color="#5F0D0D">Identity Card</h3>
<strong>(i) </strong>In order to enjoy the status and privileges of a bona fide student of the Institute, each
student must obtain an Identity Card from the office of the Dean of Students Welfare at
the time of registration or afterwards as per the notification.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(ii)</strong> Identity Card is valid for the period stamped on it.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(iii) </strong>A loss or the theft of the card should be immediately reported. A duplicate Card will be
issued by the Dean of Students Welfare on request after depositing a fee ` 50/in
theAccount Section of the Institute.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><font color="#5F0D0D">Railway Concession</h3>

This Facility is available to only regular students of the Institute<br/><br/>
<strong>(i) </strong>The railway concession orders are issued by the office of the Dean of Students Welfare to the
students for to and fro journey to their home towns during official vacations, educational tour
and vocational training. For this purpose ‘Home Town’ is defined as the native place where
the parents or if parents are not alive the guardians of the students normally reside and which
is mentioned on the Identity Card.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(ii)</strong> A Change of address is usually not allowed after the issue of Identity Card except in special
circumstances, such as, transfer of parents/guardians in service. The railway concessions for
home town are issued normally once in a semester.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(iii)</strong> To obtain railway concession, a student must apply on a prescribed application form at least
one week in advance. Railway concession will be given to the students on production of
Identity Card in person.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(iv)</strong> Any improper use of railway concession orders may invite action apart from any disciplinary
action which the railway authorities may deem fit.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(v)</strong> A student must show his identity Card for verification by the Station Master or by the railway
authorities during the journey.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><font color="#5F0D0D">DRESS/UNIFORM</h3>
The students are supposed to keep themselves neat and tidy. They are advised not to wear loose
dresses which may be unsafe for working near the machines or be uncomfortable for outdoor field
work. The B.Tech, MCA and M.Tech full time boys students must wear prescribed uniform which
consists of white shirt, steel grey trousers, black shoes with white shocks, plain maroon tie and
navy blue blazers(during winters). The prescribed uniform for girl students is steel grey Kurta,
white Salwar with white Dupatta, black shoes/sandles and navy blue sweaters(during winters).<br/><br/>

<h3><font color="#5F0D0D">CONDUCT & DISCIPLINE</h3>
Students are required to maintain a high standard of discipline and to follow the Institute rules
strictly. The competent authority may revise and notify the conduct rules in the interest of the
institute and students as and when necessary.<br/><br/>
A Student will be liable for punishment as per rules inforce
for acts of misbehavior, misconduct and
indiscipline which, in any manner are subversive to the normal functioning of the Institute and are
against the general interest of the Institute and the students. The following are deemed, but not
limited to, to be the acts of indiscipline:<br/><br/>
<strong>(i)</strong> Disregard of Institute/Hostel Rules, Orders & Notices.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(ii)</strong> Disregard of orders and instruction of staff members.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(iii)</strong> Noisy, disorderly and obnoxious behavior.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(iv)</strong> RAGGING OF JUNIOR STUDENTS.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(v) </strong>Persistent negligence of Study.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(vi) </strong>Participation in strikes and agitations.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(vii)</strong> Irregular attendance and unauthorized absence from classes and hostel.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(viii)</strong> Indulging in violent activities.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(ix)</strong> Students shall be responsible for all the tools, apparatus, instruments and materials etc issued
to them.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(x)</strong> Students shall observe all safety precautions. The Institute is not responsible for accident of
any nature in the Institute, hostel, workshop and laboratory or play ground.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(xi)</strong> Students are strictly warned not to go to Gomti River for taking bath or swimming. If any such
incident is brought to the notice of authority, such students will be liable for severe
punishment.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>(xii)</strong> No society, association or club shall be formed by the students without prior permission of the
Director.<br/>
<br/>
</p>]]></string>

    <string name="student_body1"><![CDATA[<p><h3><font color="#5F0D0D">Professional & Social Bodies</h3>
</p>]]></string>
    <string name="student_body2"><![CDATA[<p><h3><font color="#5F0D0D">Council of Student Activities</h3>

<p>The Council of Student Activities (CSA) aims to promote and develop extra curricular Activities of students.It organizes various games, sports, exhibitions and other extra curricular activities.There are in all five Sub Councils under C.S.A.<br/>
    <br/>

  At KNIT, the focus is always on developing complete individuals capable of taking the initiative in varied social and professional activities. A number of communities related to extra-curricular activities are active in KNIT which are run and managed by the students themselves.<br/>
  <br/>
  Students thus have the opportunity to sparkle their creative talents.At KNIT, students from diverse cultural, social and economic backgrounds come together to work as cohesive teams.This teamwork extends to areas out-side academics-to music, theatre, games,literary activities in the form of clubs and societies.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
</p>]]></string>
    <string name="academic_admission"><![CDATA[<p>
<h3><font color="#5F0D0D">Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech) Programmes</h3>


<ul class="Asd1">
<li><strong>(1) Eligibility Requirements</strong> &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<span class="email_lnk">    </span><br>
  As notified by the State Government of Uttar Pradesh. </li><br>
  <li><strong>(2) Mode of Admission</strong><br>
    <strong>(i)</strong> The admission to <strong>First Year B.Tech. and M.C.A. Programmes</strong> will be made through
the counseling conducted by Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University based on the merit of
candidates in the Uttar Pradesh State Entrance Examination (UPSEE)
except for <strong>Other State
Nominees</strong> which are nominated by the Government of India.<br>
<strong>(ii)</strong> The candidate after participating in the counseling is required to report at the institute on
the date mentioned in the Allotment letter.<br>
<strong>(iii)</strong> The Candidate is required to submit the following documents at the time of reporting at
the Institute for registration:

  </li><br><ul class="UL2">
<li>Allotment Letter issued by UPSEE</li>
<li>Admit Card by SEE-AKTU, if admit card is submitted at counseling centre, then
photocopy of the admit card</li>
<li>Original Certificate of high School (for proof of the age)</li>
<li>Original mark sheet of qualifying (10+2) examination</li>
<li>Original Character Certificate in prescribed format
issued by Head of the Institute last attended</li>
<li>Original Transfer / Migration Certificate of the Institute last attended.</li>
<li>Category Certificate (If opted for reservation)</li>
<li>SubCategory
Certificate if applicable</li>
<li>Weightage Certificate if applicable</li>
<li>Medical certificate in prescribed format</li>
<li>Income Certificate from those candidates (Gen/OBC/SC/ST/Minorities) whose
parents’/guardians’ annual income from all the sources is ` one lac or less than
` one lac.</li>
<li>Receipt of fee deposited at counseling centre</li>
<li>Two Passport Size Photographs</li>
<li>Medical certificate in prescribed format</li>
<li>Affidavit In case of gap in studies</li><br>
<strong>Two Sets</strong> of photocopies of all the documents/certificates mentioned above are also
required to be submitted along with two recent passport size colour photographs
  <br><strong>&nbsp;&nbsp;(iv)</strong> No direct admission are made to Second Semester of First Year or subsequent years
of the course, except for the Diploma Holders & B.Sc. graduates who are admitted to
Second Year (third semester) through the counseling conducted by the A.K.T.U on the basis of merit of candidates in SEE-AKTU
</li>
<br><strong>&nbsp;&nbsp;(v)</strong> Admission on migration/ transfer from other University/College is not permitted.
</li>
<br><strong>&nbsp;&nbsp;(vi) </strong>Domicile requirement, age limit and medical standards are the same as prescribed in<br>
  the information Brochure of SEE-AKTU<br>
</li><strong>(3) Reservations</strong><br>
&nbsp;&nbsp;(As notified in the Information Brochure of SEE-AKTU
<br><br>
</ul>
</ul>
</ul>
<br>
  <h3><font color="#5F0D0D">Master of Computer Application (M.C.A.) Programme</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>(i)</strong> Eligibility Requirements <br>As notified in the information Brochure of SEE-AKTU.</li><br>
<li><strong>(ii)</strong> Mode of Admission <br>Mode of admission to MCA programme is same as for the Undergraduates Programme.</li><br>
<li><strong>(iii)</strong>Reservations <br>As notified in the information Brochure of SEE-AKTU.</li>
</ul><br><h3><font color="#5F0D0D">M.Tech.(FullTime)Programmes</h3>
Admission to the above mentioned
programmes is made on the basis of merit of the valid
GATE Score by AKTU, Lucknow. However, in case of non-availability
of sufficient GATE
qualified candidates, NON GATE
candidates can be considered on vacant seats.</li>
</ul><br><h3><font color="#5F0D0D">M.Tech. (PartTime)
Programmes</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>(a) Eligibility Requirements</strong><br>The eligibility requirements shall be as per norms of Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University, Lucknow.</li>
<br><li><strong>(b) Mode of Admission</strong><br>Admission is made on the basis of merit of a candidate in the written test / interview
conducted by the department concerned on a specified date.</li>
</ul><br><h3><font color="#5F0D0D">Doctoral Programmes</h3>
<p><ul>
<li><strong>(a)Eligibility Requirements</strong><br>The eligibility requirements are as per the norms of Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University, Lucknow.</li><br>
<li><strong>(b)Mode of Registration</strong><br>The application for registration is required to be made on the prescribed application form
of U.P. Technical University,Lucknow.</li>
</ul></p>
</p>]]></string>

</resources>
